<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>asyncial</title>
    <link>https://asyncial.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on asyncial</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 22:20:57 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://asyncial.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Backup your current Vivaldi session automatically</title>
      <link>https://asyncial.github.io/blog/backup-your-current-vivaldi-session-automatically/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 22:20:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asyncial.github.io/blog/backup-your-current-vivaldi-session-automatically/</guid>
      <description>As you might know, I use Vivaldi. I really like it, because I think, it is a quite flexible window manager. I can have tens and hundreds of tabs open, but I can sort them, group them, view them as a tree, even tile them. Vivaldi has a downside though. It is not exactly the most stable browser on my system. So, from time to time, Vivaldi crashes and loses all my tabs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speed up URxvt</title>
      <link>https://asyncial.github.io/blog/speed-up-urxvt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 01:27:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asyncial.github.io/blog/speed-up-urxvt/</guid>
      <description>This blog post documents really quick, how you can get URxvt to be ready in less time. I measured the time, my computer needed, to start instances of URxvt to a usable shell and close it again for 25 times. I tried that with bash, dash and zsh with and without oh-my-zsh. It measured it with time(1). My test script looks like this:
#! /bin/sh for i in 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 do urxvt -e &#39;dash&#39; done Of course, &amp;lsquo;dash&amp;rsquo; needs to be replaced with the shell, you want to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Status of the Qt desktop</title>
      <link>https://asyncial.github.io/blog/the-status-of-the-qt-desktop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 15:03:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asyncial.github.io/blog/the-status-of-the-qt-desktop/</guid>
      <description>In the last few years, Qt-based desktop environments became more and more popular. There are quite a lot of them now. Of course, we have the old, trusty KDE, now in version 5.10, as &amp;ldquo;flagship&amp;rdquo; of the Qt crew, but there are more. LXQt as the lightweight choice, which is a fusion between LXDE and Razor-Qt, the highly experimental Liri, trying to implement a very modern looking desktop, very similar to Google&amp;rsquo;s Material Design, the &amp;hellip; different DE, called theShell, of course Lumina mainly targeted at *BSD, but of course portable enough, to run on Linux too, and Budgie is going to be Qt-based in the future as well!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>links</title>
      <link>https://asyncial.github.io/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 01:42:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asyncial.github.io/links/</guid>
      <description>There are a few sites, I want to recommend.
Interesting Open-Source Projects  Alpine Linux Adélie Linux Krita Postmarket OS Redox OS  Interesting Websites  nixers installGentoo wiki DistroWatch DistroChooser TextEditors wiki cat-v document archive  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>organize your .xresources</title>
      <link>https://asyncial.github.io/blog/organize-your-.xresources/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 18:52:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asyncial.github.io/blog/organize-your-.xresources/</guid>
      <description>If you are anything like me, you like to customize your terminal colorscheme. And if you are even more like me, you are using urxvt and need to edit your ~/.Xresources to changes your terminals colors. So I assume your .Xresources are mess and you want to know, how to get them clean and easy to read and customize. If you already have a working system, there is no need to change it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 more distros</title>
      <link>https://asyncial.github.io/blog/10-more-distros/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 18:50:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asyncial.github.io/blog/10-more-distros/</guid>
      <description>I’ve looked at ten more Linux distros! Again, I have the urge to share my experiences with the ca. 15 different visitors my blog already had, because I guess, they are very interested in my texts here. Or they are not. I only know one of them, and I didn’t ask him. However, here is the list of the distros:
 Alpine Linux 3.4.3 Chakra Linux 2016.02 Ian Linux Mint Debian Edition 2 NixOS 16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>casual distroreviews</title>
      <link>https://asyncial.github.io/blog/casual-distroreviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 18:47:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asyncial.github.io/blog/casual-distroreviews/</guid>
      <description>In the last few weeks, I took a look at 17 different Linux distributions. Why? Because I had nothing else to do and thought it was interesting to see, how the different systems feel. For the first round of this, I looked more at out-of-the-box, beginner-friendly-ish distros, because I’m lazy. I don’t want to say something about all of these distributions, but only about those, which were interesting or special in some way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>how to debrand your xperia z3</title>
      <link>https://asyncial.github.io/blog/how-to-debrand-your-xperia-z3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2016 18:23:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asyncial.github.io/blog/how-to-debrand-your-xperia-z3/</guid>
      <description>When I got myself a new Z3 the other day, it had a T-Mobile software branding. I think, you know what that means: stupid bloatware and less chance to get updates. So I decided to get rid of it. That’s how you do it:
 Do a back up of your data! Get and install the Sony PC Companion, if you don’t already did. Get and install Flashtool. I recommend using the torrent link, because the download server was quite slow, when I tried it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>