<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fixed on asyncial</title>
    <link>https://asyncial.github.io/fixed/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fixed on asyncial</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 15:16:32 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://asyncial.github.io/fixed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Plan 9 -&gt; Linux</title>
      <link>https://asyncial.github.io/plan-9-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 15:16:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asyncial.github.io/plan-9-linux/</guid>
      <description>Plan 9 from Bell Labs is one of the more interesting operating systems out there. I&amp;rsquo;ve always found it interesting to find software, that is in some way inspired by Plan 9 on other operating systems. So, to document what I find on this, I decided to make a list of Plan 9 inspired Linux programs.
Ports This category gets the straight-up ports of Plan9 programs to Linux/Unix out of the way, before going further.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kritische Informatik | Critical Computer Science</title>
      <link>https://asyncial.github.io/kritische-informatik-critical-computer-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 16:32:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asyncial.github.io/kritische-informatik-critical-computer-science/</guid>
      <description>Einführung | Introduction
Fehlende Innovationskraft und Hypekultur | Hype and the Lack of Innovations  The Future of Programming by Bret Victor [EN][VID] AI Winter is well on its Way by Filip Piekniewski [EN] AI Winter - Update by Filip Piekniewski [EN] Blockchain study finds 0.00% success rate and vendors don&amp;rsquo;t call back when asked for evidence by Andrew Orlowski [EN] Two in five &amp;lsquo;AI startups&amp;rsquo; essentially have no AI, mega-survey of nearly 3,000 upstarts finds by Andrew Orlowski [EN]  Wissenschaftliche Methode in der Softwareentwicklung | Scientific Method in Software Engineering  What we actually know about Software Development, and why we believe it&amp;rsquo;s true by Greg Wilson [EN][VID] Design Principles behind Smalltalk by Daniel H.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>links</title>
      <link>https://asyncial.github.io/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 01:42:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://asyncial.github.io/links/</guid>
      <description>There are a few sites, I want to recommend.
Interesting Open-Source Projects  Alpine Linux Adélie Linux Krita Postmarket OS Redox OS  Interesting Websites  nixers installGentoo wiki DistroWatch DistroChooser TextEditors wiki cat-v document archive  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
